<review assignmentNumber="1" exercises="3">

	<reviewers>
		<reviewer email="md-fahad.hasan@stud.uni-bamberg.de" matrikelnummer="2043989"> </reviewer>
		<reviewer email="stefan-wolfang.raab@stud.uni-bamberg..de" matrikelnummer="2033352"> </reviewer>
		<reviewer email="abdullah-al.faiyaz@stud.uni-bamberg.de" matrikelnummer="2034094"> </reviewer>
		<reviewer email="anne.schwarz@stud.uni-bamberg.de" matrikelnummer="1804723"> </reviewer>
	</reviewers>

	<GroupMembers>
		<member email ="mohammed-mostakim.ornob@stud.uni-bamberg.de" matrikelnummer="1985610"></member>
		<member email ="watina.malek@stud.uni-bamberg.de" matrikelnummer="1985631"></member>
		<member email ="reem-eslam-mohamed-mekky.khalil@stud.uni-bamberg.de" matrikelnummer="1978294"></member>
		<member email ="koshika.gaur@stud.uni-bamberg.de" matrikelnummer="1985139"></member>
		<member email ="christoph.wehner@stud.uni-bamberg.de" matrikelnummer="1983524"></member>
	</GroupMembers>

	<doneExercises>3</doneExercises>

	<reviewText>
		Exercise 1: In our eyes, the solution fits as it is. We have nothing to remark.

		Exercise 2:

		General remark: For better readability, you could make sure that keywords (such as SELECT, WHERE, AS, ...) are written consistently. Either in capital letters or the first letter in capital letters, etc.

			- Query 1: Output a stream of readings for all books in the room number 036.

			Remark: We think that your solution should work.Alternatively you could again join on the books table to gather the books. It is not specified what a “stream of readings” is in the question.


			- Query 2: Get a stream of all books that left one room to another (taken by a person FROM one room to another) in the last 30 minutes.

			Remark: We only found some syntax issues

			Select DISTINCT movedOptmized.bookID 
			From( 
				Select b.BookID As bookID, sdb.RoomNo As roomNO 
				From RFID_Stream [SIZE 30 MINUTES TIME] AS rs, Books AS b, StaticDB AS sdb 
				Where b.Tag_ID == rs.Tag_ID and sdb.ReaderID == rs.ReaderID 
			) As movedNotOptmized, ( 
				Select DISTINCT b.BookID As bookID, sdb.RoomNo As roomNO 
				From RFID_Stream [SIZE 30 MINUTES TIME] AS rs, Books b, StaticDB AS sdb 
				Where b.Tag_ID = rs.Tag_ID and sdb.ReaderID = rs.ReaderID 
			) As movedOptmized
			Where movedOptmized.bookID = movedNotOptmized.bookID and movedOptmized.roomNO != movedNotOptmized.roomNO;
			

			- Query 3: Get a stream of checked out books within the last 12 hours.

			Remark: We have nothing to remark.


			- Query 4: Return a result stream of books that were taken off shelve to a reading room and back within the last 12 hours.

			Remark: As your comment makes clear, this solution only works for a specific room. You could change this by answering the question whether the books appear in different rooms based on their presence in more than one stream.

			- Query 5: Return a result stream of books that were taken out of the library without being checked out.

			Remark: Your solution is based on the assumption that a book provides an entry every minute. This should be noted. We do not have any other remarks further.

		Exercise 3: In our eyes, the solution fits as it is. We didn't find any bug or mistake in the queries and each runs perfectly in the system. We have nothing to remark.
	</reviewText>

	<openQuestions></openQuestions>

</review>